

NGUYEN TU TINH

Phone: +84 (03)67 005 758 **Birthday:** 19/04/1999

Email: <u>tutinh.nt@gmail.com</u>

Address: Chua Lang, Dong Da, Ha Noi

SUMMARY

I'm a web developer with 1.5 years of experience in NodeJS technologies, with knowledge of Object-Oriented Analysis and Design, and Database Design.

Persistent in self-studying and learning new technologies, self-motivated, hard-working, responsible, and reliable, working effectively both independently and as a part of the team.

TECHNICAL SKILL

- Programming Language:
 - JavaScript & TypeSript
- Frameworks/ Flatforms:
 - NodeJS, ExpressJS, WebAPI, GraphQL
 - ReactJS, TailwindCSS, MaterialUI, Bootstrap
- Database Management Systems
 - MS SQL Server, MongoDB
- Others
 - Understanding of OOP methodogies.
 - Experience with CI, CD of GitLab, SVN.
 - Experience with Agile and Scrum development process.
 - Logical thinking.

EDUCATION

Le Quy Don Technical University - MTA (Ha Noi)

2017 - 2022

- Software Engineering
- CPA: 2.9

EXPERIENCE

AKB Software: 06/2022 – Present

Position: Full Stack Developer

- ChungVui chungvui.net
 - o **Project Description:** Platform for creating and sharing event template online.
 - Technology: MongoDB, NodeJS, ReactJS, TailwindCSS,...
 - Responsibilities:
 - Share knowledge and build the core architecture of the project.
 - Discussion and problem solving add useful features.
 - Design UI/UX, database schema and implement the solution.
 - Develop and fix bug based on requirements.
 - Building a system to send emails.

Foreign Language: English (Basic - 500 Toeic)

- Soft Skills:
 - Teamwork
 - Time Management
 - Quality Check
 - Flexibility in work

• NS2HN:

- o **Project name:** NS2HN Asset Maintenance Management System
- o **Technology:** GraphQL, NodeJS, ReactJS, Material UI, Bootstrap...
- Responsibilities:
 - Discussion and problem solving add useful features.
 - Develop small modules of the system
 - Develop and fix bug based on requirements.

Antbot Vietnam: 04/2021 – 03/2022

Position: Fresher Developer

VNMAC:

- Project Description: Management system to overcome the landmine situation in Vietnam.
- o **Technology:** Java Spring MVC, Jquery, Bootstrap,...
- Responsibilities:
 - Develop small modules of the system
 - Develop and fix bug based on requirements

PASTIMES AND ACTIVITIES

• In my free time, I like exercise and go experience things, finding new technologies, and working on personal projects.